corporateinformation.com 2006-06-15

# CorporateInformation Privacy Policy

**

**PRIVACY POLICY**  

**

CorporateInformation.com respects the privacy of visitors to this site.  This Privacy Policy applies only to your use of this site.  We have no control over the privacy practices of other sites to which you may link from here. 

**Information We Collect**

CorporateInformation.com collects only the personal information that you voluntarily and knowingly provide to us.  In order to use our services, we only require your email address and a password.  Any other personal information you choose to provide is purely voluntary and will not affect your use of this site.

            **How We Use Personal Information**

            CorporateInformation.com and its affiliates may store and use your personal information for any of the following purposes:

            -            To protect against unauthorized access to our site;

            -            To respond to your questions;

            -            To inform you of other products and services of our affiliates;

            -            To send you occasional information related to the economy or stock markets;

            \-             To administer the web site.

**_CORPORATEINFORMATION.COM WILL NOT SELL OR LEASE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO ANY THIRD PARTY.   _**

**Cookies and Statistical Information**

            Like many other web sites, CorporateInformation.com uses “cookies” to facilitate automated activity, to determine how visitors use our web site and to determine which features to add to our web site. If you instruct your browser to disable cookies, you will not be able to access CorporateInformation.com’s extensive database. The data we collect through cookies provides us with important nonpersonal information about how our site is used.  This information may be shared with our advertisers, but only in aggregate form without revealing any personal information about you or any of our visitors.

            **Links**

            CorporateInformation.com contains thousands of links to other web sites.  Since we have no control over such sites, we are not responsible for information you may provide to them, knowingly or otherwise.  Be sure to check the privacy policy of any site asking you for personal information.

            **Changes and Opting Out**

            From time to time, CorporateInformation.com may change this privacy policy.  To keep up-to-date on any changes, please check this site periodically.  If at any time you have a question about this privacy policy or you wish to opt out of access to CorporateInformation.com’s services, please Contact Us with your request.
